<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Sampath Dechu</title>
    <link>https://sampathdechu.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Sampath Dechu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sampathdechu.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://sampathdechu.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sampathdechu.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Sampath Dechu Bangalore, KA, India. Ph # 9739839457 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>https://sampathdechu.github.io/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sampathdechu.github.io/education/</guid>
      <description>
   Year Degree Specialization University Location     2001-2003 Master of Science Computer Engineering Iowa State University Ames, IA, USA   1997-2001 B.Tech Electronics and Communication Engineering J.N.T.U Hyderabad, Telangana, India    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://sampathdechu.github.io/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sampathdechu.github.io/experience/</guid>
      <description>2014 - Now Research Manager IBM Research Bangalore, KA India   At IBM research in Bangalore, I am responsible for research efforts in the areas of application of AI for business process automation and optimization. I lead the team of researchers, data scientists and software engineers to infuse AI into IBM offerings in Automation space. We have 10 published papers in top rated peer-reviewed conferences and journals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>https://sampathdechu.github.io/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sampathdechu.github.io/papers/</guid>
      <description>AI for Business process automation and optimization  Chandresh Kumar Maurya, Neelamadhav Gantayat, Sampath Dechu, Tomás Horváth: Online Similarity Learning with Feedback for Invoice Line Item Matching, Intelligent Process Automation Workshop, AAAI 2020. Tanmayee Narendra, Prerna Agarwal, Monika Gupta, Sampath Dechu: Counterfactual Reasoning for Process Optimization Using Structural Causal Models, BPM Forum 2019. Neelamadhav Gantayat, Giriprasad Sridhara, Anush Sankaran, Sampath Dechu, Senthil Mani, Gargi Banerjee Dasgupta: *Towards Creating Business Process Models from Images, ICSOC 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patents  </title>
      <link>https://sampathdechu.github.io/patents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sampathdechu.github.io/patents/</guid>
      <description>
   # id title status     1 US-10367645-B2 Proof-of-work for smart contracts on a blockchain Granted   2 US-8515725-B2 Characterization of nonlinear cell macro model for timing analysis Granted   3 US-10396375-B2 System and method for condition monitoring of redox flow batteries using data analytics Granted   4 US-9980099-B2 Indoor location detection using ceiling patterns Granted   5 US-10664522-B2 Interactive voice based assistant for object assistance Granted   6 US-10691764-B2 Search engine optimization techniques Granted   7 US-10552426-B2 Adaptive conversational disambiguation system Granted   8 US-9853690-B1 Generating high resolution inferences in electrical networks Granted   9 US-10320190-B2 Load profile selection in adaptive dynamic islanding using batteries Granted   10 US-2018130130-A1 Autonomous peer-to-peer energy networks operating on a blockchain Application Pending   11 US-2020143299-A1 Automatically Detecting Inconsistencies Between a Business Process Model and a Corresponding Tutorial Video Application Pending   12 US-2020183961-A1 External action execution with conversational agent Application Pending   13 US-2020175114-A1 Embedding Natural Language Context in Structured Documents Using Document Anatomy Application Pending   14 US-2019180639-A1 Question generation for learning session Application Pending   15 US-2019163272-A1 Simulating tactile information for haptic technology Application Pending   16 US-2019138646-A1 Systematic Browsing of Automated Conversation Exchange Program Knowledge Bases Application Pending    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sampath Dechu</title>
      <link>https://sampathdechu.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sampathdechu.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About my passion and expertise: I am passionate about building technology solutions for boosting employee productivity in enterprises. My expertise lies in design, build and deployment of data-driven computational software solutions and platforms.
About my technical experience: I have developed and delivered products that included advanced computational software methods such as: combinatorial search, numerical optimization, graph theory, data mining, statistical inference, natural language procesing, machine learning, deep learning. I have experience of developing cloud-native fullstack applications using MEAN stack in microservice architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>